Omar Ali Mohamed Frontend React.js

✓ omaralimohamedomar1@gmail.com

+20 01286494837

Exemption from military service

https://omaraliomar.netlify.app/

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/omar-ali-9a4076267/

https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4

Bē https://omaraliomar.netlify.app/pages/portfolio

Profile

Hi, I'm Omar, I'm a passionate software developer. I worked as an Assistant Manager at the Virginia Hotel for 3 years. Afterward, I joined a company called Copy and Print, where I was responsible for fixing Xerox photocopier machines. During this time, I developed a passion for programming and learned CS50 and front-end. I am very enthusiastic about programming and continuously strive to expand my knowledge and skills in this field.

Education

Bachelor's degree

Faculty of Business Alexandria university undergraduate 2023 - 2024.

Skills

HTML CSS

flexbox - grid - media query - etc.

JS

Dom - Bom - Promises - APIs - ES6 - OOP - etc. **BOOTSTRAB**

react bootstrab

SASS

GIT GITHUB

REACT JS redux - redux tool kit - router - etc.

Git flow

Command Line

Projects

Movies Website

Skills: html - css -js - react - redux - bootstrap - axios - real api.

https://movies-react-project-app.netlify.app/ ☑: host https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4/movies-app ☑: code

Landing page

Skills: html - css

 $https://omaraliblack4.github.io/template-three/ \ \boxdot\ : host \\ https://github.com/OmarAliBlack4/template-three \ \ \boxdot\ : code$

Professional Experience

2019 – 2021 **Photocopier Engineer** Alex, Egypt *Alfa Copy - Copy print*

I worked as a Photocopier Engineer at Alfa copy company in 2019.

2017 – 2019 Hotel manager assistant

Matrouh, Egypt Virginia Hotel

I worked as an assistant manager in Matrouh for a period of 3 years.